// quality:
// 0 - did not remember 😭
// 1 - vague idea 😖
// 2 - recalled with important errors 🤔
// 3 - recalled with slight imperfection 😀
// 4 - recalled correctly 😁
// 5 - easy perfect recollection 😎

module.exports = {
    decks: [
        {
            id: "0",
            name: "Vocaboli spagnolo",
            cards: [
                {
                    front: "red",
                    back: "rojo",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 0,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "orange",
                    back: "naranja",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 1,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "yellow",
                    back: "amarillo",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 2,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "green",
                    back: "verde",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 3,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "blue",
                    back: "azul",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 4,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "purple",
                    back: "púrpura/morado",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 5,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "brown",
                    back: "marrón",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 6,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "black",
                    back: "negro",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 7,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "grey",
                    back: "gris",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 8,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "white",
                    back: "blanco",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 9,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "pink",
                    back: "rosa",
                    category: "colours",
                    id: 10,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "habitaciones",
                    back: "rooms",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 11,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cuartodebaño",
                    back: "bathroom",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 12,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "dormitorio",
                    back: "bedroom",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 13,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "comedor",
                    back: "diningroom",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 14,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "pasillo",
                    back: "hall",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 15,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cocina",
                    back: "kitchen",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 16,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "salón",
                    back: "livingroom",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 17,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "abajo",
                    back: "downstairs",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 18,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cochera",
                    back: "garage",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 19,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "jardín",
                    back: "garden",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 20,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "escaleras",
                    back: "stairs",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 21,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "arriba",
                    back: "upstairs",
                    category: "house",
                    id: 22,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "aseo",
                    back: "toilet",
                    category: "house - bathroom",
                    id: 23,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "bañera",
                    back: "bath",
                    category: "house - bathroom",
                    id: 24,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "espejo",
                    back: "mirror",
                    category: "house - bathroom",
                    id: 25,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "ducha",
                    back: "shower",
                    category: "house - bathroom",
                    id: 26,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "jabón",
                    back: "soap",
                    category: "house - bathroom",
                    id: 27,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cama",
                    back: "bed",
                    category: "house - bedroom",
                    id: 28,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "silla",
                    back: "chair",
                    category: "house - bedroom",
                    id: 29,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "lámpara",
                    back: "lamp",
                    category: "house - bedroom",
                    id: 30,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "repisa",
                    back: "shelf",
                    category: "house - bedroom",
                    id: 31,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "estantería",
                    back: "shelves",
                    category: "house - bedroom",
                    id: 32,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "armario",
                    back: "wardrobe",
                    category: "house - bedroom",
                    id: 33,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cocina",
                    back: "cooker",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 34,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "taza",
                    back: "cup",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 35,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "tenedor",
                    back: "fork ",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 36,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "frigorífico",
                    back: "fridge",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 37,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "vaso/copa",
                    back: "glass",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 38,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cuchillo",
                    back: "knife",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 39,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "microondas",
                    back: "microwave",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 40,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "plato",
                    back: "plate",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 41,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cuchara",
                    back: "spoon",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 42,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "mesa",
                    back: "table",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 43,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "lavadora",
                    back: "washingmachine",
                    category: "house - kitchen",
                    id: 44,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "sillón",
                    back: "armchair",
                    category: "house - livingroom",
                    id: 45,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "reloj(pared)",
                    back: "clock",
                    category: "house - livingroom",
                    id: 46,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "sofá",
                    back: "sofa",
                    category: "house - livingroom",
                    id: 47,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "televisor",
                    back: "television",
                    category: "house - livingroom",
                    id: 48,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "video",
                    back: "video",
                    category: "house - livingroom",
                    id: 49,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "banco",
                    back: "bank",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 50,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "cafeteria",
                    back: "café",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 51,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "carnicería",
                    back: "butcher's",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 52,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "farmacia",
                    back: "chemist's",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 53,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "lavandería",
                    back: "laundry",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 54,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "librería",
                    back: "bookshop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 55,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "panadería",
                    back: "baker's",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 56,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "parada de autobus",
                    back: "bus stop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 57,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "pastelería",
                    back: "cake shop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 58,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "peluquería",
                    back: "hairdresser's",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 59,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "supermercado",
                    back: "supermarket",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 60,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "tienda de ropas",
                    back: "clothes shop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 61,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "tienda de discos",
                    back: "record shop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 62,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "tienda de deportes",
                    back: "sports shop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 63,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "zapatería",
                    back: "shoe shop",
                    category: "city",
                    id: 64,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "ahoy",
                    back: "today",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 65,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "mañana",
                    back: "tomorrow",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 66,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "ayer",
                    back: "yesterday",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 67,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "anoche",
                    back: "last night",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 68,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "anteayer",
                    back: "the day before yesterday",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 69,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "el día",
                    back: "the day",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 70,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "la semana",
                    back: "the week",
                    category: "days",
                    id: 71,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "la primavera",
                    back: "the spring",
                    category: "days - seasons",
                    id: 72,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "el otoño",
                    back: "the autumn",
                    category: "days - seasons",
                    id: 73,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "el verano",
                    back: "the summer",
                    category: "days - seasons",
                    id: 74,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "el invierno",
                    back: "the winter",
                    category: "days - seasons",
                    id: 75,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "lunes",
                    back: "Monday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 76,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "martes",
                    back: "Tuesday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 77,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "miércoles",
                    back: "Wednesday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 78,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "jueves",
                    back: "Thursday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 79,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "viernes",
                    back: "Friday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 80,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "sabado",
                    back: "Saturday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 81,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "domingo",
                    back: "Sunday",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 82,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
                {
                    front: "el fin de semana",
                    back: "the weekend",
                    category: "days - week",
                    id: 83,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: null,
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
            ],
        },
        {
            id: "1",
            name: "Other",
            cards: [
                {
                    front: "test front",
                    back: "test back",
                    id: 0,
                    repetitions: [],
                    lastSchedule: null,
                    nextRepeat: new Date(),
                    factor: 2.5,
                    isRepeatAgain: false,
                },
            ],
        },
    ],
}
